Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Office of the Dean of Students
UWM Archival Collection 48
28.2 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Collection contains records of the Dean of Students from the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee (UWM) and its predecessor institutions. The collection also contains records from the UWM Office of Student Life and from the UWM Student Organization Advising and Resources (SOAR) office. Most of the records date from the 1960-1982; the materials predating 1960 concern fraternities and sororities. The collection largely consists of files of UWM student organizations, including fraternities and sororities, student government, and a wide variety of ethnic, political, professional, religious, and social groups. Most of the files contain only a charter application form and a group registration form, which lists the name and function of the group, its off-campus affiliation, meeting location, names and addresses of officers, and faculty advisor. Some files contain officer change reports, a constitution and by-laws, correspondence, newsclippings, photographs, and publicity materials. The most extensive files exist for campus fraternities and sororities, and Vietnam-era protest groups. Files also exist for a number of student groups for African Americans, Hispanics, and women. The most recent addition to the collection consists of a large number of files related to the Student Association and disciplinary issues with some of its members and officers. Also included are subject files dealing with official policies of the Office of Student Life, such as on on-campus protests, as well as dealing with campus issues such as racism and student stress.
The Office of Student Affairs was established in 1956 when UWM was created. The head of the office was officially called the Dean of Student Affairs, but was often informally called the Dean of Students until 1974. The official Office of the Dean of Students was established in 1974 following the resignation of David W. Robinson as Dean of Student Affairs. Between 1974-1979, the Dean of Students reported to the Assistant Chancellor for Student Services and Special Programs. After 1979, the Dean reported to the Assistant Chancellor for Student Affairs.
Effective July 1, 1994, Student Organization Advising and Resources separated from the Office of Student Life.
Dean of Students
1974-1975 Vacant
1975-1979 Barrie Wight
1979-1996 Carmen M. Witt
1996-1998 James Hill (Interim)
1998-2006 James Hill
2006-2007 Tom McGinnity (Interim)
2007-2009 James Hill
2009-2010 Tom McGinnity (Interim)
2010-2011 James Hill
2011-2013 Tom McGinnity (Interim)
2013- Timothy Gordon
Records documenting fraternities and sororities can be found under the name of the organization, and files on Fraternities, Fraternity Scholarship Reports, Greek Week, Interfraternity Council, Inter-Greek Council, Inter-Sorority Council, Panhellenic Council, Policies and Regulations Governing Greek Houses and Lodges, Sororities, and University Student Government.
Records documenting African American student groups (not including fraternities or sororities) can be found for the African Liberation Support Committee; Afrika Incorporate; Black Achievement Organization; Black Critic; Black Cultural International Association; Black Political Caucus; Black Student Organization of the School of Social Welfare; Black Students Psychological Association; Minorities for Wood; Minority Business Students Association; Minority Coalition; Project Black; Society for the Advancement of Future Minority Doctors; Students Against University Racism; and United Black Student Front.
Records documenting Hispanic student groups (not including fraternities or sororities) can be found for the Amigos De Las Americas; Groupo Estaudiantil Puertorriqueno; Imagen Latina; Latinos Unidos; League of United Latin American Citizens; Los Universitarios; Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan; and Ray Mendoza Defense Fund.
Records documenting the administration of UWM student publications can be found under Crossroads, Friends of Kaleidoscope, Ivy Publications, Panther Courier, and Tempest/Cheshire Literary Magazine.
Records documenting Vietnam War-era protest groups (not including fraternities or sororities) can be found for the April 24th Committee; Campus Committee for Peace in Asia; Demonstrations; Friends of the Indochinese People; Milwaukee Organizing Committee; Student-Faculty Committee To End The War In Vietnam; Students for a Democratic Society; Students to Support Milwaukee 14; Students United for a Strong Stand in Vietnam; UWM Anti-War Committee; UWM Community Vietnam Moratorium Committee; and Vietnam Veterans Against the War.
Records documenting women's student groups (not including fraternities or sororities) can be found for the Associated Women Students; Business and Professional Women at UWM; Campus Campaign for ERA; Dames Club; Feminist Center of UWM; Feminists for Life of Wisconsin; Intercollegiate Association of Women Students; Milwaukee Women's Rugby Football Club; Prime Time for Women; Students in Support of Women's Athletics at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee; Task Force on the Status of Women in Student Affairs at UWM; University Women's Council; Women for Wood; Women Writers' Collective; Women's Health Coalition; and Women's Liberation.
The collection also contains includes information regarding the Office of Student Life's interactions with the UWM Student Association. In addition to meeting packets, these files also include lists of committee assignments, informational and policy materials, and correspondence between the Dean of Students and Student Association officials.
Included in the records are a small number of administrative records of the Office of Student Life. These records consist of annual reports of the activities of the office and its interactions with students, as well as subject files on other departments in the Division of Student Affairs, including the Klotsche Center, Parking and Transit, and campus religious centers. Also in this part of the collection are policies and subject files on major issues facing campus, such as campus protest, racism, dealing with cults recruiting on campus, and the Office's response to on-campus student death.
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
The collection is arranged into two series:
Student Organization Files, 1915-2010
Subject Files, 1959-2012
Students often used different versions of a name for their organizations. For the sake of standardization in the finding aid, the files in Series 1 are listed alphabetically by the name listed on the charter, constitution, or group registration form.
Series 2 is organized alphabetically by subject.
A spreadsheet with file-level information on the electronic records is available in the Archives department. The spreadsheet contains information on file size, dates created and modified, file format, and software used to create the file. Additional technical metadata is available; consult an archivist for more information.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
UW-Milwaukee Student Involvement Records UWM Archival Collection 170
UW-Milwaukee Student Association Records UWM Archival Collection 113
UW-Milwaukee Student Affairs, Office of the Assistant Chancellor Records UWM Archival Collection 58
UW-Milwaukee Student Affairs, Office of the Vice Chancellor Records UWM Archival Collection 201
Administrative/Restriction Information
Electronic files must be viewed on computers in the Archives. Contact an archivist for more information.
The student organization files in series 1 are restricted as stipulated in the Privacy Act of 1974, 5 U.S. Code, Section 552 (a). However, the Office of the Dean of Students has extended to the Archives its permission to provide access to redacted copies of restricted records, following guidelines established by the Office of Legal Affairs and the UWM records custodian.
There are no other access restrictions on the remainder of the materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
An unknown individual transferred most of the collection to the Archives prior to 1989. Merry Demske transferred 2 cubic feet of student organization files (accession 1991-018) to the Archives in November 1991. The provenance of the records is unclear. Many of the early records in the collection were created or compiled by the Dean of Men and the Student Activities Coordinator. It is not known if these records were later brought together by the Dean of Students or if they were separated from other files by University or Archives staff. The records, whatever their provenance, were placed together under the office of the Dean of Students by the Archives staff sometime before 1989. When processing began in 1993, it was decided to leave the existing organization intact rather than to possibly confuse the provenance even more.
In July 1995 additional student organization records were added to the collection. The records appear to have been created largely by the Office of the Dean of Students, though at some time they were organized into record groups by type of student organization (i.e.. cultural, political, religious, etc.). Pamela in Carmen Witt's office transferred accession 1994-018 to the Archives in December 1994.
Brian Jacobson transferred accession 1993-019 to the Archives in March 1994, Rebecca Loss from the SOAR office transferred accession 1995-026 in November 1995, Tammy Jannette transferred accession 1995-048 in May 1996, Rebecca Loss transferred accession 1996-010 in August 1996, Rebecca Loss transferred accession 1996-021 in November 1996, and Jennifer Swartz transferred accession 1997-027 in November 1997. The Office of Student Life transferred accession 2010-001 to the Archives in July 2010. The Office of Student Life donated additional materials (accession 2010-069) in June 2011.
As of May 24, 2013, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core 2 Duo CPU (2.33 GHz, 1.95 GB RAM) running Windows XP Professional Version 2002, with Service Pack 3. Adobe Reader XI was used to access the files.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Acrobat PDF 1.4 - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Contents List
- Records, 1915-2012, UWM Archival Collection 48; 28.2 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - 1. Student Organization Files, 1915-2010
    The entirety of this series is restricted under the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974. See an archivist for more information.
    - AA at UWM, 1977-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - A-Cad User Group, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Acapella Choir of UWM, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Acceleration Club, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Access Party, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Accuracy in the Academics of Reporting, 1985-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Achieving Student Action Through Progress, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - ACME Poetry, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - ACOA/AI-ANON/ACODF Women's Group, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Actors' Guild at UWM, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Admission Events, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Adventures Outdoors (UWM), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adversary, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Advertising Club at UWM, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Advocates for Life at UWM, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Advocates for Truth, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - African Liberation Support Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - African Students Association, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Afrika Incorporate, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Agenda, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Task Force at UWM, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Aikido Yoshinkai Club, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - ALANON/ACOA Welcome Home Group, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Aldo Leopold Conservation Club
      - 1962-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Activities, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Financial Records, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alioto for Alderman Student Chapter, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Alioto for President Campaign Committee, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Alive at UWM, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - All Night Klub (TANK), 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - All Night Party, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alliance for Animals, 1983-1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Alliance of Computer Enthusiasts at UWM, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Allied Health Program Student Organization, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Allied Health Student Association, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Angel Auxiliary Club, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Alpha Chi, 1970-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alpha Chi Rho, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Alpha Delta, 1951-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Alpha Delta Mu
      - 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - 1978-1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Alpha Delta Sigma, 1943-1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Alpha Epsilon Phi, 1959-1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi
      - 1956-1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - 1957-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Alpha Gamma Lambda, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Alpha Kappa Lambda, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alpha Kappa Psi, 1957-1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi
      - 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - 1958-1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Alpha Phi, 1957-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Alpha Phi Omega
      - 1959-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
      - 1968-1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Alpha Sigma Alpha, 1950-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau, 1975-1986 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Alpha Tau Delta, 1976-1986 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Alpha Tau Omega, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Alpha XI, 1982-1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Alternative, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Alternative Axis Productions, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Alternative Broadcasting Systems, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Alternative Concerts Group, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Alternative Energy for a Poetic Future, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Alternative Journalism Society, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Alternative Publications, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Alternative Recreation Club, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Alternative Writers Workshop at UWM, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - American Counseling Association, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - American Friends of Revolutionary Iran at UWM, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - American Indian Graduate Council, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - American Indian Student Movement, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1972-1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - American Institute of Architects Student Chapter, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - American Institute of Architecture Students, 1968-1994 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - American Marketing Association, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - American Medical Student Association, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - American Nazi Party, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - American Nuclear Society, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - American Society for Information Science, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - American Society for Personnel Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - American Society for Training and Development, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - American Society of Interior Designers, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - AMICI, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Amiga Bittmappers, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Amigos De Las Americas, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Amnesty International, 1985-1993 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Analytical Psychology Fellowship at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Anna V. Day Dorm, 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Anthropology Club, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Anthros, 1960-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - APICS, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Apostolic Student Fellowship, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - April 24th Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Aqualens Cinema, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Arab Students Association, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Armenian Cultural Association, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Ars Musica, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Art Circle, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Art Club, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Art History Forum, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Art, Music and the Theatre, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Art of Listening Ensemble, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Art Student Cooperative, 1973-1985 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Art Students' League
      - 1957-1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - 1992 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Art Students' Travel Association, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Artactics, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Artists for Peace in Vietnam, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Arts in Action, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Assassination Information Bureau, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Associated Students of UWM, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Associated University Broadcasters, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Associated Women Students, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Association for Childhood Education, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Association International of Students in Science of Economics and Commerce, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Association of Advanced Students in Education, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - ATID, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Association of Black Artists, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Association of Computing Machinery, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Association of Interdisciplinary Studies, Audit, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Association of Students for Architecture, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Association of Women in Social Welfare, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Athletes in Action, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization Alumni Association, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Baccalaureate Student Nurses Organization of UWM, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - BACCHUS (Boost Alcohol Consciousness Concerning the Health of University Students), 1984-1993 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Backpacking Club, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Badminton Club, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Baha'i Club, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Ballroom Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Bands at UWM, 1957-1987 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Bangladesh Student Association at UWM, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Barely United Graduate Zoologists, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Baseball Club, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Be Proud UWM, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Beach Party, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Beer Party, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Believe, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Beta Chi
      - 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - 1962-1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Beta Gamma Sigma, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Beta Phi Theta, 1924-1957 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Beta Pi, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Beta Sigma Psi Gamma, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Beta Tau Omego, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Biological Action Group, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Biological Science Organization, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Biology Club, 1940, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Biomedical Society, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Bite Humor Society, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Black Achievement Organization, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Black and Gold, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Black Critic, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Black Cultural International Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Black Graduate Council, 1981-1988 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Black Mass Media Society, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Black Political Caucus, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Black Student Organization of the School of Social Welfare, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Black Students Psychological Association, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Black Students' Union, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Blue Key, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Bolton Hall Graduate Student Association, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Bringing Excellence and Educational Reform, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Brotherhood Association of Independents, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Brotherhood of Ambitious Independents, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Brown for President Student Committee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Buddhist Studies and Meditation Group, 1982-1989 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Business and Professional Women at UWM, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Business Oriented Student Society, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Camera Club, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Campus Action Party, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Campus Action Program, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Campus Activities Board, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Campus Advance, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Campus Affiliates of Project Youth, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Campus Arts Council, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Campus Bible Fellowship, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Campus Bible Study
      - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 80)
      - 1994 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Campus Campaign for ERA, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Campus Carnival, 1951-1971 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Campus Chess Club, 1958-1985 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Campus Coalition for President Ford, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Campus Committee for Peace in Asia, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Campus Conservatives Club, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Campus Ecology for Education, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Campus Entertainment Organizers, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Campus Events Board (CEB), 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Campus Gamers Organization, 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Campus Gold, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Campus Graphics, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Campus Heterosexual Union, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Campus Party, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Campus Satelite, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Canterbury Association of Episcopal Students, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cardinal Club, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Cardinal Compass, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Cardinal Party, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Care for Cambodia, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - CASE Student Organization, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Caving Club, 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Ceramic Club, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Cercle Francais (French Club), 1957-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Chamber Orchestra, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Change Progress and Reform, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Cheap Trips, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Cheerleading Squad of UWM, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Cheshire, 1957-1964, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Chess Club of UWM, 1958-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Chess Masters, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Chi Alpha, 1969-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chi Beta Epsilon, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Chi Sigma Lambda, 1954-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Chinese Bible Study Group, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Chinese Book Club, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Chinese Christian Fellowship at UWM, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Chinese Student Library, 1978-1990 (Box 17, Folder 86)